Hello.
こんにちはー
Are you nervous?
緊張してますか?
yes.
はい
LOL Your smile is wonderful.
笑 笑顔が素敵ですね
what are you doing?
何してるの?
Just from your name.
ちょっとお名前からで
I'm Mian.
ミアンです
Mian-chan.
ミアンちゃん
Do you know what we're going to do today?
今日これから何するか分かりますか?
Dizzy?
ぼちぼち?
What's the content?
内容は何ですか?
content.
内容
内 容
Sexy?
エッチ?
Sex with an uncle.
おじさんとエッチ
I feel refreshed today.
今日さっぱりしてますね
Is it Telekakushi?
テレカクシですかね
So, when is tomorrow?
じゃあ、あすたきいつですかね?
Form two.
中二
Secondary 2?
中二?
14 years old.
14歳
Quite a while ago, isn't it?
結構前、早いですね
Is it early?
早いですかね
Who is your opponent?
相手は何?
gentlemen?
先生?
No, my friend.
いや、友達
friend?
友達?
He's not my boyfriend.
彼氏ではないんだ
yes.
はい
Were you friends and you were like, let's do it at home?
友達で、家でやっちゃうぞ、みたいな感じでやったの?
Well, I guess that's okay.
まあ、いいかな、みたいな
How was it?
どうでした?
it was fun.
楽しかった
Did it feel good?
気持ちは良かった?
It felt good.
気持ちは良かった
Fellatio and that?
フェラと、あれですか?
Did you insert it?
挿入したんですか?
yes.
はい
It's been quite a while since then, and are you guys having sex constantly?
それ から結構経って、お前たちコンスタントにエッチしてます?
Yeah.
うん
Fair enough.
まあまあ
Do you like sex?
エッチは好きな子?
I like it.
好きです
Uncle, will you do your best today?
おじさん、今日頑張ります?
I will do my best.
頑張ります
That's right, it's an H cup.
あれなんですけど、Hカップですよね
yes.
はい
Wait, when did you get so big?
ちょっと、いつから大きくなったの?
Small 4?
小4?
That's amazing.
すごいね
From 4th grade?
小4から?
Me.
自分ね
That's amazing.
すごいですね
Looks good on your face.
顔に似合う
Is it really about the same?
ほんと同じぐらいですか?
How about a second helping of one?
片方のおかわりは
I don't know.
分かんない
The way it's done is sloppy.
され方が雑ですね
Shall I open it up a bit?
ちょっと開けてみようか
H cup?
Hカップか
That's amazing.
すごいね
Ah, about this.
あ、こんぐらいで
I felt like I was being eloquent.
明弁感出ちゃって
close.
近い
It seems a little tight, so please scoop it up a little.
ちょっと、きつそうなんで、ちょっとすくってあげて、
Breasts.
おっぱいや
So, has this grown up since 4th grade?
じゃあ結構、これ小4から大きくなったの?
yes.
はい
It feels like you can see it all at once.
一気な目で見られる感じだ
Have you been told that your breasts are adult?
おっぱい成人とかって言われた?
Are you being bullied?
いじめられてはいないか
I'm not being bullied.
いじめられてはない
Was it touched?
触られた?
It's really natural.
ほんと天然だね
Try bulging.
ブルブルってしてみて
She's beautiful, boobs.
美女だよね、おっぱい
Even though it's an H cup.
Hカップなのにね
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Please give it a try.
ちょっと、寄せてみて
Can I use both hands?
両手でいいですか?
May I hold your hand for a moment?
ちょっと手を挟んでもらおうか
It's soft.
柔らかいです
Do you also do paizuri?
パイズリとかもしてますか?
sometimes.
たまに
Sometimes.
たまにね
So, can I have you lick my nipples for a moment?
じゃあちょっと自分の乳首を舐めてもらっていい?
Can you do it?
できるかな?
please.
お願いします
I ate it.
食った
It's heavy.
重いね
It's tough.
大変だね
It's really cool.
すごいかっこいいですね
Have you gotten used to it yet?
もう慣れた?
like
若
Dry.
干
Does it tickle?
く すぐったいか?
tickles.
くすぐったい
I end up playing with it.
遊んでしまうの
Please wait a moment.
ちょっと待ってください
Lose weight.
痩せて
Please come in.
入ってください
I don't really understand it though.
よくわかんないですけどね
What about Creature?
クリーチャーどうですか?
Are you eating?
食べてます?
I'm eating.
食べてます
Are you going to turn me into a woman over the phone?
電話とかで女にするの?
do not.
しない
I tried expanding it myself a little.
ちょっと自分で広げてみたら
Na.
な
I thought I'd try expanding it myself.
自 分で広げてみたらな
You're sleeping.
寝てますね
That's how it sounds.
音はそうなんですね
Drink your own breasts.
自分でおっぱい飲んで
Will the cat come home too?
猫も帰るかな?
This?
こ っち?
It certainly came out great.
確かにすごい出てきた
確 か に すごい 出 て きた
Will the cat come home too?
猫も帰るかな?
Let me close this for a moment.
ちょっとこっち閉めらせて
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
A little creature.
ちょっとクリーチャー
Was it moving?
動いてたか?
moving
動 いて
Taka?
た か?
Was it good?
よ くよかった?
Please
お願いしまー
vinegar.
す
I'm fine.
元 気ですよ
Is Shin-chan hard?
しんちゃん硬い?
Just go over there.
ちょっとそっち行って
How are you doing?
元気ですかね?
not present?
いない?
Dad looks like he's coming in.
お父ちゃん入りそう
Dad should go to bed.
お父ちゃん寝よっかじゃ
He looks a little happy.
ちょっとうれしそうですもん